sheldoncomics.com 2005-11-25

# Comics.com Privacy Policy

|  |  |  | 

|  |   |   |   |   |   |   |   |   |   
---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---  
|  |   
|  |   
---  
|   
|  |    
PRIVACY STATEMENT

At United Media, we believe that greater protection of personal privacy on the web will not only protect consumers but also increase consumer confidence, ultimately increasing participation in online activities. We endeavor to educate users about how to protect their privacy when using the Web. Our information collection practices are described below.

Comic Basic (Free Services).  
When a user registers for Comic Basic, services available to our users at no charge, certain personal information is collected and retained after registration is successfully completed. This information is: user name, e-mail address, zip code, gender and age.Comics Extra (Premium Services).  
When a user registers for Comics Extra, premium services available to our users for a subscription fee, certain personal information is collected and retained after registration is successfully completed. This information is: user name, e-mail address, zip code, gender, age as well as payment and billing information including credit card and billing address information.Send a Strip and E-cards.  
Comics.com, and all its related brands and sites, welcome all of its users to send comic strips and e-cards to their friends. While users are required to provide their names and e-mail addresses to utilize these services, that information is only temporarily retained by United Media. It is also forwarded to the recipients of the comic strips and e-cards. Use of Information.  
We may disclose personally identifiable information to third parties when required by law or in the event such information is relevant to judicial or government investigations or proceedings, or otherwise necessary to protect our website or the safety of its users. Finally, United Media may also use information obtained from cookies to perform statistical analyses of aggregate user behavior, but personally identifiable information is not used in that instance. We may use that information for internal purposes to improve content and design, and share it, in the aggregate, with advertisers. Cookies.  
Cookies are information files that your web browser places on the hard drive of your computer when you visit a website. Cookies were designed to help a web site recognize the prior visits to a site made by a user's browser. Cookies cannot damage user files, pass on computer viruses, capture e-mail addresses or read information from a user's hard drive. At Comics.com, we do not store any personal information into cookies nor do we link or combine information collected through cookies to any personal information that is submitted online when participating in our activities.Third Party Advertising  
We use MaxOnline and other third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please click here

<http://www.maxonline.com/privacy_policy/index.php>

Third Party Cookies  
In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique “cookie” on your browser.Changing Your Cursor.  
Comics.com, and all its related brands and sites, provide its users a direct link to Comet Systems, Inc.'s website, which enables users to change their cursors. That link is <http://files.cc.cometsystems.com/cc2/utilities/8/help/faq_cc.html>. Before enjoying this service, users should view Comet System Inc.'s privacy policy at <http://www.cometsystems.com/privacy/>.Advertisers, Partners and Third Party Content Providers.  
Comics.com, and all its related brands and sites, provide links to other websites, such as those of our advertising partners and Third Party content providers, including but not limited to web search-engine providers, that may have their own information collection practices. These other websites are governed by their own privacy policies or information collection practices, which may be substantially different from ours. We encourage visitors to review the privacy policies and information collection practices of those websites.Security.  
United Media uses its best efforts to ensure the security of personal information submitted by its users. All forms used for the submission of personal information are secure and all user data is stored in a secure environment.Use of Materials.  
The right to download and store or output the materials in our site is granted for the user's personal use only, and materials may not be reproduced in any edited form. Any other reproduction, transmission, performance, display or editing of these materials by any means mechanical or electronic without the express written permission of us is strictly prohibited. Users wishing to obtain permission to reprint or reproduce any materials appearing on these sites may contact us at [reprints@unitedmedia.com](mailto:reprints@unitedmedia.com).Customer Contacts.  
United Media reserves the right to email any free or premium subscribers information regarding important issues and/or changes related to their accounts. Questions and How Users Can Correct Information.  
If you have any questions, comments or concerns regarding Comics.com's privacy policy and/or practices, or you need to correct personal information, please write to us at: United Media  
Attn: Web Privacy Policy  
200 Madison Avenue  
New York, NY 10016  
Or e-mail us at:  
[customerservice@comicmembers.com](mailto:customerservice@comicmembers.com)This policy is effective as of August 1, 2003. Any change will be posted at the earliest possible time and shall apply to all personal information submitted after the effective date of such change.

To link to the full Terms of Use Agreement pertaining to our site, please click here.

The [Comics.com](http://www.comics.com/) website is intended for domestic viewers and is consequently directed towards residents of the United States.

|   
---|---|---  
  
|  |   
---|---
